Hey guys, you had a few things to
buenos chavales tenías que unas cosillas
say about the end of the year. Okay, it
que comentaron sobre el fin de año vale
seemed ridiculous to me on
que me pareció ridículo por parte de
Spanish television. Of course, I
televisión española yo por supuesto lo
saw it. I saw it on Spanish television. Okay,
vi lo vi en televisión española vale
because seeing the options we had, we didn't
porque viendo las opciones que teníamos
have
tampoco que fuera tampoco teníamos
much choice either.
grandes opciones no
Ana Obregón's words didn't impact me much. I did
me impactaron mucho las palabras de ana
n't even cry
obregón no se me saltaron las lágrimas
as a parent with the things she said. I'm not
como padres con las cosas que dijo no
going to show you the audio because, well, you
voy a poneros el audio porque bueno ya
know how to really piss people off in front of
sabes cómo tocar los [__] frente de
the TV. I could put it on. You know, I
la tele podría ponerlo yo sabe que
always put on all the TV stuff
siempre pongo todas las cosas de la tele
and all that.
y demás
But there's one thing that's quite curious
pero hay una cosa bastante curioso
if you see this scene.
si veis esta escena en esta
The flowers they put up, they put
las flores que han puesto la han puesto
a band of flowers, okay, much
una banda de flores vale muchísimo más
wider and taller than usual
ancha y más alta que la de costumbre
to cover the Spanish flag that
para tapar la bandera española que
was projected. I mean, there was a
estaba proyectada o sea había una
projected flag. Okay, he told us, he took
bandera proyectada vale nos decía cogido
some images where you can see it, but
alguna imagen donde se vea pero la
Puerta del Sol had projected a
puerta del sol había proyectado a una
Spanish flag. Okay,
bandera española ok
well, those from Spanish television, which, as you
pues los de televisión española que ya
know, is a public TV station owned by the government.
sabéis que una tele pública del gobierno
Juan Antonio, thank you very much. They
juan antonio muchísimas gracias
always put flowers here. Okay, but they've
siempre ponen flores aquí vale pero
never put them up so high. Okay,
nunca las ha puesto tan altas vale
just covering the flag
justo tapando la bandera
because people  he is offended by the flag
porque a la gente le ofende la bandera
of his country, I mean, you go, you go to
de su país o sea tú vas tú vas a
any country, okay, you go to the US and the
cualquier país vale tú vas a eeuu y la
US flag is everywhere, it's
bandera de eeuu está por todas partes
everywhere. In fact,
está por todas partes de hecho
look at
mira
Ignacio Escobar, pay attention
ignacio escobar atención a esto ayuso
to this, Ayuso orders the Spanish flag to be projected on the Puerta del Sol during the broadcast of the chimes. My God, how can he be so fascist? Oh my God, what a boycott, what a boycott, putting the Spanish flag projected on the Puerta del Sol. No, it's not like every
puerta del sol no no es como si en todos
country feels proud of their
los países se sintieran orgullosos de su
flag and does the same thing. No, it's
bandera e hicieran lo mismo no
just that I saw it at the Eiffel Tower,
ostia es que yo en la torre eiffel lo
man, I
visto ojo de bs tío
mean, at the Eiffel Tower, I saw a
o sea en la torre eiffel lo he visto un
lame guy, they challenged the nonsense he is criticizing,
cojo desafiaron la tontería que critica
okay, but look at what a
vale pero fijaros qué acto tan
repugnant act on the part of
repugnante por parte de televisión
Spanish television. No, how good, Spanish television
española no qué bueno televisión
is the same as Place ETA,
es lo mismo que place eta
RTVE, okay, we have already criticized it on
rtve vale ya lo hemos criticado en
several occasions, remember that at Place
varias ocasiones acordaros que en place
ETA they gave coverage to him and what they
eta dieron difusión a él y lo que le
did to Dallas,
hicieron a dallas
the psychologist, do you remember that?  they released a
la psicóloga os acordáis que sacaron una
news story, well, look at the news they
noticia sea fíjate la noticia que
released a week before, they were
sacaron una semana antes estuvieron
making a video with Forza talking
haciendo un vídeo con forza hablando
about the cancellation
sobre la cancelación
but then they published a thread about a
pero después publicaron el hilo de una
random person who came out to defame with
persona random que salió para difamar a
bullets okay but look how
balas vale pero fijaros que es
disgusting this fact is, Abrego doesn't ring the
repugnante este hecho no dan ábrego las
bells everyone is excited with
campanadas todo el mundo emocionado con
the coat with her words okay and Ana
el abrigo con sus palabras vale y ana
Obregón becomes a trending topic
obregón se hace trending topic durante
all night until the next day because of
toda la noche hasta el día siguiente por
the moment okay people start
el momentazo vale la gente empieza a
uploading clips of Ana Obregón to Twitter
subir a twitter clip de ana obregón
sending kisses to her son may he rest in peace
mandando los besos a su hijo que en paz
and look what she does with
y mirad lo que hace con televisión
Spanish television, let it be a complaint from the
española que sea una denuncia del
copyright holder the
titular de los derechos de autor el
copyright holder of this
titular de los derechos autor de este
clip is Spanish television okay, I mean
clip es televisión española vale ósea
when this tweet starts to be viewed
cuando se empieza a visualizar este tuit
with this clip they
con este clip
report it for copyright a [ __ ] tweet
lo denuncian por copyright un [__] tuit
a [ __ ] tweet that nobody profits from
un [__] tuit del que nadie se lucra
okay
vale
with what intention do they think they do this,
con qué intención creen que hacen esto a
the impression I get is that
mí la impresión que me da es de que
they want
quieran que se visualice
Abrego's work to be seen okay but that they can only
lo de ábrego vale pero que sólo puedan
go see it on the
ir a ir a verlo a la página de
Spanish television page,
televisión española
incredible  incredible incredible like for
increíble increíble increíble como por
example this dude I mean I saw this
ejemplo esto tío o sea esto lo he visto
on twitter okay I don't know if the lyrics of the
en twitter vale no sé si la letra de la
song is that it's not clear to me if
canción es que no me queda claro si
anyone saw it please explain it to me
alguien lo vio por favor que me lo
but they put a lot of screenshots
explique pero han puesto muchas capturas
on twitter that this was seen in the
en twitter de que se veía esto en los
subtitles of a program that is made in
subtítulos de un programa que se hace en
sides that also belongs to
lados que pertenece también a televisión
Spanish television we put a program made with
española ponemos un programa hecho con
singers no singers come out singing
cantantes no salen cantantes cantando
a lot of songs no and apparently
montón de canciones no y por lo visto
in the subtitles I came out to this but I don't know
en los subtítulos salí a esto pero no sé
if the subtitles came out
si salían los subtítulos
or also in the lyrics of the song
o también en la letra de la canción
the edge of crazy vox I mean but I am a
el filo de loco vox o sea pero yo es una
public television that we all pay for now
televisión pública que pagamos todos ya
but was it the lyrics of the song too
pero era la letra de la canción también
or just the subtitles
o sólo los subtítulos
was it just the subtitles
era solo los subtítulos
man me in Argentina if you don't have a
hombre yo en argentina si no tienes una
flag from there they give you and they take away your
bandera de allí te dan y te quitan el
Argentine license face with your mouth
carnet de argentino cara con la boca
open
abierta
that the Spanish flag offends you dude
que te ofenda la bandera española tío
being from Spain
siendo de españa
it would
la
offend me it would affect me with
a mí me ofendería a mí me afectaría a
other things okay three other
otras cosas vale otros tres han puesto
agents of Podemos have put in these days that I'm not
agentes de podemos en estos días que no
going to put them in this  air video
los voy a poner en este vídeo de aire
for another video because I'm collecting
para otro vídeo porque estoy recopilando
but
pero
people from Podemos these days have
gente de podemos en estos días han
posted tweets
puesto tweets
celebrating things and praising people,
celebrando cosas y alabando a gente
characters
personajes
Javi, those are great pills of humor,
javi esas son pildorazos de humor
pills or humor
píldoras o de humor
these are great pills of humor
estos son pildorazos de humor
this was put to use by the bricklayers of
esto le puso al uso a los albañiles de
his hospital over the PA system and saying it is heard
su hospital por megafonía y decir se oye
according to a report from the Civil Guard the
según un informe de la guardia civil la
fault was the chachachá and the 8m demonstration
culpa fue del chachachá y de la mani de
the dance reproduces the rare ability of
el baile reproduce la rara habilidad de
Pepe and Box to shake hands and turn their backs at the
pepe y box darse la mano y la espalda al
same time
mismo tiempo
God it is a public television for all
dios es una televisión pública de todos
Spaniards whatever ideology they
los españoles tengan la ideología que
have we all pay for it
tengan la pagamos todos
this is incredible no this is incredible
esto es increíble no esto es increíble
in recent days we have seen several
en los últimos días hemos visto varios
tweets the president of the government and
tweets el presidente del gobierno y
Salvador and already several ministers ministers
salvador y ya varios ministros ministros
of health
de sanidad
addressing Ibai okay thank you and he goes
dirigiéndose a ibai vale gracias y va
there for the work you do
ahí por la labor que haces
thank you and he goes to and today we have seen without a doubt
gracias y va a y hoy hemos visto sin
that Salvador and already surely that
seguro que salvador y ya seguro que
Salvador and he has already seen the chimes on
salvador y ya ha visto las campanadas en
the device channel this is a lie several I am
el canal device esto es mentira varios
going to explain why if Salvador Villa
voy a explicar por qué si salvador villa
had seen the chimes on
hubiera visto las campanadas en el canal
Ibai's channel what  would have done would be to
de ibai lo que habría hecho sería
take a picture of the television and not
hacerle una foto a la televisión y no
a screenshot on the mobile phone, I would have taken a
una captura al móvil hubiera hecho una
picture on the television in his house at the
foto en la televisión de su casa en el
time of the bells, not a screenshot on the
momento de las campanadas no una captura
mobile phone, this screenshot, the mobile phone has been
el móvil esta captura el móvil le ha
put there for posturing because what
puesto por postureo porque lo que
we are using is ibai okay they are
estamos utilizando es a ibai vale están
trying to use the vice to
intentando utilizar el vice para para
get votes from the youth okay me 6
conseguir votos de la juventud vale yo 6
direction man I don't know what yes yes yes there are
dirección hombre no sé que sí sí sí sí
kids there I don't know who to vote
hay chavales hay no sé a quién votar
for well he has made that they support and vice like that that place like that easy and neither the cyber nor follows him this is incredible it turns out that I don't know what it is from podemos but I don't know what exactly mario herrera in mares his bmw against a tree in the middle of
potras su bmw contra un árbol en pleno
curfew and runs away like a rabbit I didn't
toque de queda y huye como un conejo no
know I knew that the
lo sabía yo sabía que había salido las
photos of the car had come out the bmw embedded from
fotos del coche empotrado el bmw por
behind
atrás
and apparently the guy left instead of
y por lo visto el tío se fue en vez de
calling the ambulance the civil guard
llamar a la ambulancia la guardia civil
has gone whatever it is he left I don't know why
ha ido lo que sea se fue no sé por qué
if to avoid some evidence or whatever I
si para evitar alguna prueba o lo que no
have no idea but the case that left
tengo ni idea pero el caso que se fue
okay and this headline like rubén sánchez
vale y este titular osea rubén sánchez
from facua that sticks  all day
de facua que se pega todo el día
making headlines about politics
poniendo en titulares sobre política
when they're things like we can't make them
cuando son cosas así de podemos no las
public, not on your Twitter, it doesn't
públicas no en su twitter no
stay with me waiting for us and here the acne that he
me queda esperándonos y aquí el acné que
posted has done the search and off he goes,
ha puesto ha hecho la búsqueda y se vaya
gem, friend Mario, let's see the tweets
joyita el amigo mario a ver los tweets
dear Cospedal, it's not that I hate you but
querida cospedal no es que te odie pero
if you had a fire in your house and
si tuvieras un incendio en tu casa y
there was water I would drink it
tuviese agua me la bebería
how beautiful how beautiful
qué bonito qué bonito
look what he does he puts out a press release they
fijaros lo que hace saca una nota de
put out a press release rtve.es and look at
sacan una nota de prensa rtve.es y mirad
the clip,
el clip
I mean like I was at this moment okay at
osea como ibai en este momento vale en
this moment it was trending on Twitter
este momento era tendencia en twitter
okay
vale
what they do is they compile the
lo que hacen es recopilamos los
characters that we've talked about the most
personajes de los que más hemos hablado
in 2020 and now he puts I don't know who, a
en 2020 y ahora pone no sé quién la un
little bit talking about who it is and Vice is
cachito hablando de quién es y vice es
a streamer who has achieved
un streamer que este año ha conseguido
a lot of success this year, double talking about reviving it.
mucho éxito doble hablar de revivirla
Hello, hello Cristiano, how are you? Will you post the
hola hola cristiano que tal fijará en el
clip
clip
so that people believe that the
para que la gente se crea que las
chimes have been on site so that
campanadas han sido a sitio para que la
people believe that they are going to click on it to
gente se crea que le van a dar click a
see who it is and Vice today every
ver quién es y vice hoy cada las
chime looks at the books,
campanadas mira los book
man, how sad, how sad
tío qué triste qué triste
and well, little  They talk about this marvel
y bueno poco se habla de esta maravilla
that what shocks me is that they have
que lo que me choca es que esto lo hayan
left this on Spanish television
lo hayan dejado en televisión española
you know after all this they
sabes después de todo esto como un [__]
have left the great José Mota like a bug who has
han dejado al gran josé mota' que haga
made this wonderful video worth
hecho este vídeo maravilloso vale para
jumping the cop and surely but I don't care I
saltar el cop y seguramente pero me da
think
yo creo
mediocre there is
mediocre
a mediocre in me
hay un mediocre en mí
when you went to vote you gave me
cuando fuiste a botar tú me diste
while well they do
mientras
n't deceive him to put him there he
pues no lo engañan para ponerlo ahí él
is progressive
es progre
he is progressive
él es progre
although I suspected that progress and the
aunque yo sospechaba que progress y lo
progres and
de progrés y
if I suspected it
si lo sospechaba
no problem I will remedy because to
ningún problema voy a remediar porque a
me
mí
[Music] there is
[Música]
a mediocre in me
hay un mediocre mí
the ballot boxes blows weapons
las urnas golpes armas
again me mascots
de nuevo me botargas
and I am literally literally I mean
y yo es literalmente literalmente o sea
when they come back the ballot box will vote again
cuando vuelvan la urna volverá a votar
year the kings
año los reyes
[Music]
[Música]
what gave me there is
que me dio
a mediocre last there is
hay un medio último
a mediocre in me
hay un mediocre en mí
of course what a shame I still don't know
desde luego qué vergüenza todavía no sé
why we have the politicians that we have there is
por qué tenemos los políticos que
a mediocre in you there
tenemos hay un mediocre en ti
is a mediocre in you
hay un mediocre en ti
when you went to vote you gave me
cuando fuiste a votar tú me diste
while
mientras
no problem because you have finished with
ningún problema porque has terminado con
Joan Vich now John pinchao radio and
joan vich ahora john pinchao radio and
plan we have finished it is a while
plan hayamos terminado es un rato
Incredible, wonderful video by José
increíble maravilloso vídeo de josé
Mota. Guys, I'm
mota' chavales
going to watch the last song. I'm already
voy a ver el último tema ya me voy
wrapped up in this live thing with the
enrollado con esto del directo de los
hijas. Incredible, incredible. I'm
hijas increíble increíble estoy flipando
still freaking out. I
todavía
'm still freaking out that Joan
estoy flipando todavía con que joan
Planas was here watching us the whole
planas haya estado aquí viéndonos todo
live stream, trying to hide the Boada video.
el directo intentando ocultar el vídeo